# **Dewanda Robinson**

3204 Hunter Park Circle, apt. H Fort Worth, Texas 76116 (414) 380-0959 mswandaone@yahoo.com

# SCHEDULER/COORDINATOR

# Coordination | Administrative Support | Patient Care

Versatile nursing health care professional with extensive experience coordinating the logistics of health care for a variety of patients in a variety of settings. Able to combine previous scheduling and certified nursing assistant experience to deliver outstanding results. Recognized for the ability to effectively coordinate activity within fast-paced, dynamic environments balancing patient needs with organizational guidelines. A strong communicator, able to develop strong relationships with patients, staff and administration to support overall health care goals.

### **Areas of Expertise**

Healthcare Regulations
Doctor Interactions
Administrative Assistance
Communication
Patient Assessment
Healthcare Informatics
Medical Documentation
Patient Engagement
Customer Service
Patient Advocacy
Microsoft Office Suite

#### **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATION**

**Bachelor of Arts, Health Care Management** – Concordia University, Milwaukee, WI (2013) GPS: 3.7/4.0

Medical Billing and Coding Certified - Herzing University, Brookfield, WI (2014)

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**COVANCE,** Dallas, Tx **Research Technician** Present

2016 -

2016 - 2017

#### NURSECORE MANAGEMENT, ARLINGTON, TX

Certified Nursing Assistant (CNA)

Travel to a number of different facilities assisting elderly patients with a variety of daily living activities.

#### AMADA SENIOR CARE, DALLAS, TX

2016 - Present

#### Certified Nursing Assistant (CNA)

• Spend time with a depressed elderly patient, assisting her with a number of tasks including store and doctor visits.

#### FROEDTERT HOSPITAL, MILWAUKEE, WI

2004 - 2015

#### Certified Nursing Assistant (CNA)

- Assisted patients with everyday tasks post surgery including eating and bathing while helping doctors and nurses with a variety of clinical procedures.
- $\cdot \quad \text{Developed a working knowledge of medical terminology}.$
- Responsible for a variety of tasks including drawing blood, accurately entering patient information into the EPIC system, emptying blood drains, setting up IV fluids, assisting with CT scans and assisting nurses transporting patients.
- · Monitored suicide patients at risk for harming themselves and elderly and cancer patient with a variety of mental issues.
- · Obtained experience working with trauma patients.

## ST. MARY HOSPITAL, MILWAUKEE, WI

2001 - 2004

#### Scheduler/Healthcare Coordinator

- Delivered exceptional service while answering phones and processed patient paperwork related to discharges and transfers.
- · Scheduled procedures including testing and X-rays and ordered medical/office supplies.
- Accurately processed doctor orders as requested.

ATLAS BUS COMPANY, MILWAUKEE, WI Dispatcher

• Successfully supervised 25 drivers, delegating assignments and assisting with direction and the location for drivers.

# **COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT**

Volunteer – Boys & Girls Club